<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<data>
<version>3.0 Free</version>
<books>
<book>
<bookid>4</bookid>
<isbn>0553803719</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[Foundation]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[Isaac Asimov]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Spectra]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>2004-06-01</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>11</hits>
<rating>4</rating>
<price>18.00</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>256</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Foundation-Isaac-Asimov/dp/0553803719%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D0553803719]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/4181H430GQL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:16:50</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br />One of the great masterworks of science fiction, the Foundation novels of Isaac Asimov are unsurpassed for their unique blend of nonstop action, daring ideas, and extensive world-building. The story of our future begins with the history of Foundation and its greatest psychohistorian: Hari Seldon.  <br><br>For twelve thousand years the Galactic Empire has ruled supreme. Now it is dying.  Only Hari Seldon, creator of the revolutionary science of psychohistory, can see into the future—a dark age of ignorance, barbarism, and warfare that will last thirty thousand years. To preserve knowledge and save mankind, Seldon gathers the best minds in the Empire—both scientists and scholars—and brings them to <br>a bleak planet at the edge of the Galaxy to serve as a beacon of hope for future generations. He calls his sanctuary the Foundation.<br><br>But soon the fledgling Foundation finds itself at the mercy of corrupt warlords rising in the wake of the receding Empire. And mankind’s last best hope is faced with an agonizing choice: submit to the barbarians and live as slaves—or take a stand for freedom and risk total destruction.<br /><strong>Amazon.com Review</strong><br /><I>Foundation</I> marks the first of a series of tales set so far in the  future that Earth is all but forgotten by humans who live throughout the  galaxy.  Yet all is not well with the Galactic Empire. Its vast size is  crippling to it.  In particular, the administrative planet, honeycombed and  tunneled with offices and staff, is vulnerable to attack or breakdown. The only person willing to confront this imminent catastrophe is Hari Seldon, a  psychohistorian and mathematician.  Seldon can scientifically predict the  future, and it doesn't look pretty: a new Dark Age is scheduled to send  humanity into barbarism in 500 years.  He concocts a scheme to save the  knowledge of the race in an Encyclopedia Galactica.  But this project will  take  generations to complete, and who will take up the torch after him?  The first Foundation trilogy (<I>Foundation</I>,   <I>Foundation and  Empire</I>,  <I>Second Foundation</I>)  won a Hugo Award in 1965 for "Best All-Time Series."  It's science fiction  on the grand scale; one of the classics of the field. <I>--Brooks  Peck</I><br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1276</categ></categs>
</book>
<book>
<bookid>5</bookid>
<isbn>0345330137</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[Double Star]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[Robert A. Heinlein]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Del Rey]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>1986-10-12</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>21</hits>
<rating>0</rating>
<price>7.99</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>256</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Double-Star-Robert-Heinlein/dp/0345330137%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D0345330137]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51NQIijLHmL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[First Thus]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:16:22</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br />One minute, down and out actor Lorenzo Smythe was -- as usual -- in a bar, drinking away his troubles as he watched his career go down the tubes. Then a space pilot bought him a drink, and the next thing Smythe knew, he was shanghaied to Mars.<br><br>Suddenly he found himself agreeing to the most difficult role of his career: impersonating an important politician who had been kidnapped. Peace with the Martians was at stake -- failure to pull off the act could result in interplanetary war. And Smythe's own life was on the line -- for if he wasn't assassinated, there was always the possibility that he might be trapped in his new role forever!<br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1278</categ></categs>
</book>
<book>
<bookid>2</bookid>
<isbn>032152599X</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[PHP 6 and MySQL 5 for Dynamic Web Sites: Visual QuickPro Guide]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[Larry Ullman]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Peachpit Press]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>2007-12-29</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>50</hits>
<rating>7</rating>
<price>31.49</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>648</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/PHP-MySQL-Dynamic-Web-Sites/dp/032152599X%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D032152599X]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41NSMXp2hWL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:17:02</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br />It hasn't taken Web developers long to discover that when it comes to creating dynamic, database-driven Web sites, MySQL and PHP provide a winning open source combination. Add this book to the mix, and there's no limit to the powerful, interactive Web sites that developers can create. With step-by-step instructions, complete scripts, and expert tips to guide readers, veteran author and database designer Larry Ullman gets right down to business: After grounding readers with separate discussions of first the scripting language (PHP) and then the database program (MySQL), he goes on to cover security, sessions and cookies, and using additional Web tools, with several sections devoted to creating sample applications. This guide is indispensable for intermediate- to advanced level Web designers who want to replace their static sites with something dynamic. In this edition, the bulk of the new material covers the latest versions of both technologies: PHP 6 (due out in 2008) and MySQL 5 (available now). The book's publication date is likely to beat the official release of PHP 6, making it one of the first books available on the subject.<br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
<review>
<fk_userid>0</fk_userid>
<rating>7</rating>
<date>2010-10-29 11:56:39</date>
<title><![CDATA[anonyomus]]></title>
<comment><![CDATA[Best of the best book]]></comment>
</review>
<review>
<fk_userid>0</fk_userid>
<rating>10</rating>
<date>2010-10-29 12:34:50</date>
<title><![CDATA[Good book]]></title>
<comment><![CDATA[<p>this book very good</p>]]></comment>
</review>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1279</categ><categ>1277</categ></categs>
</book>
<book>
<bookid>1</bookid>
<isbn>1590595521</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[Beginning PHP and MySQL 5: From Novice to Professional, Second Edition (Beginning from Novice to Professional)]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[W.J. Gilmore]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Apress]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>2006-01-23</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>56</hits>
<rating>0</rating>
<price>32.84</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>952</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Beginning-PHP-MySQL-Novice-Professional/dp/1590595521%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D1590595521]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51nXccDRAVL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[2]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:15:49</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br />Book Description   <ul>    <li>Essentially three books in one, provides thorough introductions to    the PHP language, MySQL database, and shows you how these two  technologies   can be effectively integrated to build powerful websites.</li>    <li>Provides over 500 code examples, including real-world tasks such as    providing an auto-login feature, sending HTML-formatted email, testing    password guessability, and uploading files via a Web interface.</li>    <li>Updated for MySQL 5, includes new chapters introducing triggers,   stored procedures, and views.</li>  </ul>    From the Back Cover   <P>Interested in becoming a master of the PHP language and MySQL  database   but don't know where to begin? This bestselling book ranks  among the most   thorough and practical guides in print, covering all of  the key concepts   and features, and showing you how to effectively  integrate PHP and MySQL   to build powerful websites.</p>  <P>The book begins with a vast overview of PHP's capabilities, starting    with a survey of the installation and configuration process on both the    Windows and Linux platforms. Next, several chapters are devoted to  basic   PHP concepts, including variables, datatypes, arrays, functions,  string   manipulation, and processing user input. Other key PHP topics  are also   covered, including PEAR, session handling, LDAP integration,  the Smarty   templating engine, Web services, and PDO.</p>  <P>Next up is a presentation of MySQL's key features. You're first  guided   through MySQL's installation and configuration process, and are  presented   with an introduction to its storage engines, datatypes,  administration   utilities, security features, and data import/export  facilities. New MySQL   5-specific chapters have been added in this  edition, covering triggers,   stored procedures, and views. Along the  way, you'll gain insight into   PHP's assortment of MySQL functions  (using both the mysql and mysqli   extensions), and learn how to create  and execute queries, perform   searches, and carry out key database tasks  from within your Web   application.</p>    What You Will Learn from This Book   <ul>    <li>Install and configure Apache, PHP and MySQL on both Windows and   Linux</li>    <li>Accept and process information submitted via HTML forms</li>    <li>Authenticate users and track user preferences and data using PHP's   session-handling capabilities</li>    <li>Process Web-based file uploads using the HTTP_Upload PEAR   package</li>    <li>Create your own RSS aggregator using Magpie, and process XML files in   amazingly efficient fashion using SimpleXML</li>    <li>Use both command-line and graphical MySQL clients to effectively   manage your data</li>    <li>Secure the MySQL server, creating roles and restricting access even   at very granular levels</li>    <li>Effectively integrate PHP and MySQL to create dynamic, data-driven   web applications</li>  </ul>    Who This Book Is For   <P>This book is for the budding web developer searching for a powerful  and   low-cost solution to building flexible, scalable websites.</p><br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1279</categ><categ>1281</categ><categ>1277</categ></categs>
</book>
<book>
<bookid>6</bookid>
<isbn>0446696617</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[1st to Die (The Women's Murder Club)]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[James Patterson]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Grand Central Publishing]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>2005-05-20</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>42</hits>
<rating>7</rating>
<price>10.19</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>432</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/1st-Die-Womens-Murder-Club/dp/0446696617%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D0446696617]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51udawWvXIL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:16:13</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br />Imagine a killer who thinks, "What is the worst thing anyone has ever done?"--and then goes far beyond it. Now imagine four women --a police detective, an assistant DA, a reporter, and a medical examiner --who join forces as they sidestep their bosses to track down criminals. Known as the Women's Murder Club, they are pursuing a murderer whose twisted imagination has stunned an entire city. Their chief suspect is a socially prominent writer, but the men in charge won't touch him. On the trail of the most terrifying and unexpected killer ever, they discover a shocking surprise that turns everything about the case upside down.<br /><strong>Amazon.com Review</strong><br />The Women's Murder Club pits four San Francisco women professionals   against a serial killer who's stalking and murdering newlyweds in bestselling   author James Patterson's newest thriller. Lindsay Boxer is a homicide inspector   who's just gotten some very bad news. She deals with it by immersing herself in   her newest case and soliciting the personal as well as professional support of   her closest friend, who happens to be the city's medical examiner. The two   women, along with an ambitious and sympathetic reporter and an assistant DA,   form an unlikely alliance, pooling their information and bypassing the chain of   command in an engaging, suspenseful story whose gruesome setup is vintage   Patterson. <p>    "What is the worst thing anyone has ever done?" the killer muses to himself   early in the narrative. "Am I capable of doing it? Do I have what it takes?"   Answering his own question, he embarks on a murderous spree that takes him from   the bridal suite in a Nob Hill hotel to a honeymoon destination in the Napa   Valley and thence to a wedding reception at the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and   Museum in Cleveland, Ohio. Dispatching his victims on the happiest day of their   lives, he purposefully leaves enough clues for his distaff trackers to discover   his identity and put him behind bars. But just when the women think they've got   the case all wrapped up, the killer turns the tables on them in a bloody   denouement that even the most discerning reader won't see coming. Patterson,   author of the popular Alex Cross mysteries, promises future adventures for the   Women's Murder Club, which may give him an opportunity to develop his heroines'   characters more completely and win new fans among those who prefer their   detectives in high heels and lipstick. <I>--Jane Adams</I><br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1276</categ></categs>
</book>
<book>
<bookid>3</bookid>
<isbn>1590598482</isbn>
<title><![CDATA[Beginning Joomla!: From Novice to Professional (Beginning from Novice to Professional)]]></title>
<authors><![CDATA[Dan Rahmel]]></authors>
<manufacturer><![CDATA[Apress]]></manufacturer>
<releaseDate>2007-07-19</releaseDate>
<language>English</language>
<langshow>*</langshow>
<hits>98</hits>
<rating>0</rating>
<price>34.19</price>
<priceunit>USD</priceunit>
<numberOfPages>475</numberOfPages>
<url><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Beginning-Joomla-Novice-Professional/dp/1590598482%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAIWZKHN3I6UWTN3XQ%26tag%3Dorda-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D1590598482]]></url>
<imageURL><![CDATA[http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51IOJW9F5gL._SL160_.jpg]]></imageURL>
<edition><![CDATA[]]></edition>
<ebookURL><![CDATA[]]></ebookURL>
<informationFrom>1</informationFrom>
<date>2010-11-10 14:17:16</date>

<comment><![CDATA[<strong>Product Description</strong><br /><p>Do you want the ability to manage documents, photos, and other content over the Web but dont want to shell out thousands of dollars in proprietary solutions? Want to create an online community for your hobby or user group? Youre not alone. For thousands of like-minded around the globe, the answer is Joomla!, an open source content management system used to manage all sorts of data over the Web.</p>        <p>While Joomla! is relatively easy to install, a fair amount of knowledge is required in order to configure the application to your specific needs. <i>Beginning Joomla! </i>answers many of the questions youre sure to have, guiding you through the process of creating your own design templates, adding and managing content, and adding popular community features such as article commenting, user profile management, and forums. Later chapters discuss e-commerce integration, explore search engine optimization, and show you how to extend Joomla! by creating your own plug-ins.</p><br />]]></comment>
<published>1</published>
<owneremail></owneremail>
<featured_clicks><![CDATA[]]></featured_clicks>
<featured_shows><![CDATA[]]></featured_shows>
<vm_id_product>0</vm_id_product>
<reviews>
</reviews>
<categs>
<categ>1280</categ><categ>1277</categ></categs>
</book>
</books>
<categories>
<category>
<id>1277</id>
<parent_id>0</parent_id>
<title>Development</title>
<name>Development</name>
<alias>development</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>1</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
<category>
<id>1278</id>
<parent_id>0</parent_id>
<title>Favorits</title>
<name>Favorits</name>
<alias>favorits</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>2</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
<category>
<id>1276</id>
<parent_id>0</parent_id>
<title>Other</title>
<name>Other</name>
<alias>other</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>3</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
<category>
<id>1280</id>
<parent_id>1277</parent_id>
<title>Joomla</title>
<name>Joomla</name>
<alias>joomla</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>1</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
<category>
<id>1281</id>
<parent_id>1277</parent_id>
<title>MYSQL</title>
<name>MYSQL</name>
<alias>mysql</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>2</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
<category>
<id>1279</id>
<parent_id>1277</parent_id>
<title>PHP</title>
<name>PHP</name>
<alias>php</alias>
<image></image>
<section>com_booklibrary</section>
<image_position>left</image_position>
<description></description>
<published>1</published>
<checked_out>0</checked_out>
<checked_out_time>0000-00-00 00:00:00</checked_out_time>
<editor></editor>
<ordering>3</ordering>
<access>0</access>
<count>0</count>
<params>-2</params>
</category>
</categories>
</data>
